{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Cyber Security July  Password Security Quiz ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"1.\tWhich is the strongest password of the options below? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"123456 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_397","roles":{"answer":{"title":"123456\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"This1s@password! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_398","roles":{"answer":{"title":"This1s@password!\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Im@9wf4t^qr3$( ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24957_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Im@9wf4t^qr3$(\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24976","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Boodles21 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24972_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Boodles21\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct  - Answer: C  The best passwords mix numbers, upper and lowercase letters, and special characters (symbols). It’s also always best to make passwords as long as you can. Password C would take approximately 24 billion years for a bad actor to guess.  If your password is answer A, please change it. Immediately.  Source: https://www.my1login.com/resources/password-strength-test/  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: C  The best passwords mix numbers, upper and lowercase letters, and special characters (symbols). It’s also always best to make passwords as long as you can. Password C would take approximately 24 billion years for a bad actor to guess.  If your password is answer A, please change it. Immediately.  Source: https://www.my1login.com/resources/password-strength-test/  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22301","si22316","si22327","si24961","si24976","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.\tWhich is the strongest password of the options below?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si26198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_838","roles":{}},{"id":"si26095","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_795","title":"2.\tYour co-worker has forgotten her login to the shared system at work and has asked you to provide her your login credentials so she can complete her work on time. What should you do? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_826","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_827","title":"Send her your login credentials in the internal company email system. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26106_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_435","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Send her your login credentials in the internal company email system.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_828","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_829","title":"Decline, but offer to help her in contacting the company support desk. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26117_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_436","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Decline, but offer to help her in contacting the company support desk.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si26128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_830","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_831","title":"Write it down on a post-it note and hand it directly to her. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26128_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"437","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Write it down on a post-it note and hand it directly to her.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26139","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_832","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26143","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_833","title":"Whisper it in her ear, making sure nobody else is in earshot. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26139_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"439","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Whisper it in her ear, making sure nobody else is in earshot.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_837","roles":{}},{"id":"si26220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_137","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_138","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26260","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_139","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26278","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_140","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26290","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26302","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26314","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26350","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26362","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26374","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_834","title":"Correct  - Answer: B  NEVER share your password with anyone, even in a deadline situation. While sharing login credentials / passwords may seem like a quicker and easier way to get work done, it can have disastrous consequences for your organization.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_835","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: B  NEVER share your password with anyone, even in a deadline situation. While sharing login credentials / passwords may seem like a quicker and easier way to get work done, it can have disastrous consequences for your organization.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_836","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26387","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si26095","si26110","si26121","si26132","si26143","si26220","si26238","si26260","si26278","si26290","si26302","si26314","si26326","si26338","si26350","si26362","si26374","si26186"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26387"},"question":{"interactionId":"26081","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2.\tYour co-worker has forgotten her login to the shared system at work and has asked you to provide her your login credentials so she can complete her work on time. What should you do?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"3. What percentage of people use the same passwords for both work and personal accounts? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"17% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"17%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"35% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"35%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22657","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_730","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_731","title":"51% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22657_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"51%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"77% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22928_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"77%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct  -  Answer: C  Over half of all people polled use the same passwords for both work and personal accounts. If you share passwords between accounts and a cybercriminal breaches just one, they might be getting access to all your accounts. It is important to use a different password for every one of your accounts.  Source: https://dataprot.net/statistics/password-statistics/  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: C  Over half of all people polled use the same passwords for both work and personal accounts. If you share passwords between accounts and a cybercriminal breaches just one, they might be getting access to all your accounts. It is important to use a different password for every one of your accounts.  Source: https://dataprot.net/statistics/password-statistics/  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22624","si22639","si22650","si22661","si22932","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3. What percentage of people use the same passwords for both work and personal accounts?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":10}}}},{"id":"si26864","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_864","roles":{}},{"id":"si26761","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_801","title":"4. How does multi-factor authentication (MFA) help keep your accounts secure? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26772","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_852","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26776","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_853","title":"It uses something like a physical token or mobile phone app to prove you are really trying to log in.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26772_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"449","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It uses something like a physical token or mobile phone app to prove you are really trying to log in.\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26783","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_854","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26787","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_855","title":"It double checks the security protocols at the page you are logging in at to ensure the page is legitimate. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26783_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"451","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It double checks the security protocols at the page you are logging in at to ensure the page is legitimate.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si26794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_856","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26798","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_857","title":"It requires you to make a second password when logging in, making it hard to guess. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26794_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"453","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It requires you to make a second password when logging in, making it hard to guess.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_858","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26809","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_859","title":"It checks your login credentials against a central database to confirm your identity. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26805_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"455","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It checks your login credentials against a central database to confirm your identity.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_863","roles":{}},{"id":"si26886","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_145","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26904","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_146","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_147","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26944","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_148","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26956","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26968","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26980","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26992","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27004","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27028","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27040","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26828","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_860","title":"Correct  - Answer: A  MFA used a second factor (for example, a physical token, a mobile smartphone app, or even a secondary email address) to prompt you confirm that you really did attempt to login. If you are ever prompted by your MFA to confirm a login that you DID NOT initiate, change your password immediately, as it has possibly been compromised.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26840","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_861","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: A  MFA uses a second factor (for example, a physical token, a mobile smartphone app, or even a secondary email address) to prompt you confirm that you really did attempt to login. If you are ever prompted by your MFA to confirm a login that you DID NOT initiate, change your password immediately, as it has possibly been compromised.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_862","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27053","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si26761","si26776","si26787","si26798","si26809","si26886","si26904","si26926","si26944","si26956","si26968","si26980","si26992","si27004","si27016","si27028","si27040","si26852"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27053"},"question":{"interactionId":"26747","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. How does multi-factor authentication (MFA) help keep your accounts secure?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":10}}}},{"id":"si27197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_877","roles":{}},{"id":"si27094","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_802","title":"5. What percentage of people keep the same passwords after falling prey to a phishing attack? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_865","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_866","title":"12% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27105_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"457","roles":{"answer":{"title":"12%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27116","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_867","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_868","title":"30% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27116_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"459","roles":{"answer":{"title":"30%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si27127","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_869","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_870","title":"42% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27127_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"461","roles":{"answer":{"title":"42%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_871","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27142","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_872","title":"57% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27138_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"463","roles":{"answer":{"title":"57%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_876","roles":{}},{"id":"si27219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_149","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27237","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_150","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27259","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_151","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_152","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27289","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27301","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27313","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27325","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27337","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27373","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27161","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_873","title":"Correct  -  Answer: D  Most users who fall for phishing attacks do not change their passwords after they divulge them. This leaves these users open to a variety of personal consequences, such as stolen funds or identity theft. Failing to change your password after a phishing attack at work can result in enormous data breaches and thousands of exposed passwords.   Source: https://dataprot.net/statistics/password-statistics/  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_874","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: D  Most users who fall for phishing attacks do not change their passwords after they divulge them. This leaves these users open to a variety of personal consequences, such as stolen funds or identity theft. Failing to change your password after a phishing attack at work can result in enormous data breaches and thousands of exposed passwords.   Source: https://dataprot.net/statistics/password-statistics/  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_875","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27386","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si27094","si27109","si27120","si27131","si27142","si27219","si27237","si27259","si27277","si27289","si27301","si27313","si27325","si27337","si27349","si27361","si27373","si27185"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27386"},"question":{"interactionId":"27080","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5. What percentage of people keep the same passwords after falling prey to a phishing attack?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":0,"penalty":10}}}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6. True or false: A passphrase of five random unrelated words (e.g. slimecupleaveserrordoor) can be just as strong as a more complex password that is 9 characters long (e.g. J%mBX3D!#*) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"TRUE ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"TRUE\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"FALSE ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"FALSE\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct  - Answer: TRUE  Both options above would take around 2.5 to 3 thousand years to crack. When there’s no limit on password length, it’s worth considering an easier to remember passphrase over a complex password that you might forget. You can also make your passphrase stronger by mixing in some upper and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols.  Sources: https://www.my1login.com/resources/password-strength-test/ https://protonmail.com/blog/protonmail-com-blog-password-vs-passphrase/   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: TRUE  Both options above would take around 2.5 to 3 thousand years to crack. When there’s no limit on password length, it’s worth considering an easier to remember passphrase over a complex password that you might forget. You can also make your passphrase stronger by mixing in some upper and lowercase letters, numbers, and symbols.  Sources: https://www.my1login.com/resources/password-strength-test/ https://protonmail.com/blog/protonmail-com-blog-password-vs-passphrase/   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si23379","si23394","si23405","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6. True or false: A passphrase of five random unrelated words (e.g. slimecupleaveserrordoor) can be just as strong as a more complex password that is 9 characters long (e.g. J%mBX3D!#*)\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7. Which age group is most likely to use a different password for each account? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"18-24 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"18-24\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"25-35 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"25-35\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"35-50 ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"35-50\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"50+ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24830_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"50+\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct  -  Answer: D  Google found that those in the 50+ age range are the most likely to use different passwords for their online accounts. Source: https://www.comparitech.com/blog/information-security/password-statistics/   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: D  Google found that those in the 50+ age range are the most likely to use different passwords for their online accounts. Source: https://www.comparitech.com/blog/information-security/password-statistics/   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si23717","si23732","si23743","si23754","si24834","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7. Which age group is most likely to use a different password for each account?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si25607","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_825","roles":{}},{"id":"si25493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_794","title":"8. What percentage of people use a password manager? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_811","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25508","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_812","title":"9% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25504_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_429","roles":{"answer":{"title":"9%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25515","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_813","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25519","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_814","title":"24% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25515_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_430","roles":{"answer":{"title":"24%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si26029","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26033","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" 45%  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26029_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":" 45%\r\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26044","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26048","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" 60% ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26044_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":" 60%\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25601","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_824","roles":{}},{"id":"si25629","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_133","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25647","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_134","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25669","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_135","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25687","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_136","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25699","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25735","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25747","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25759","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25771","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25571","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_821","title":"Correct  -  Answer: B  Only 24% of people use a password manager, despite many saying that they need a better solution for tracking and managing their login information.  Source: https://www.comparitech.com/blog/information-security/password-statistics/   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25583","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_822","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: B  Only 24% of people use a password manager, despite many saying that they need a better solution for tracking and managing their login information.  Source: https://www.comparitech.com/blog/information-security/password-statistics/   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25595","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_823","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25796","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si25493","si25508","si25519","si26033","si26048","si25629","si25647","si25669","si25687","si25699","si25711","si25723","si25735","si25747","si25759","si25771","si25783","si25595"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25796"},"question":{"interactionId":"25473","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. What percentage of people use a password manager?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"July2021Quiz","class":"project","title":"July2021Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide22582","Slide26387","Slide22905","Slide27053","Slide27386","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide25796","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide22582q0","Slide26387q1","Slide22905q2","Slide27053q3","Slide27386q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6","Slide25796q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":50,"passScore":40}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide26387","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide27053","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide27386","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide25796","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}